You can't do this! I won't let you!
你不能这么做！我不允许你这样！
You cannot stop us.
你阻止不了我们
No one can.
没谁能
Now you're beginning to understand
the Cybermen, Vaughn.
现在你开始了解赛博人了, Vaughn
You can't make bargains with them!
你不可能跟它们做交易！
I won't let them take over, I won't!
我不允许他们接管, 我不！
You think you're indestructible?
Well, I can destroy all of you!
你觉得你们是无法战胜的？好, 我要摧毁你们全部！
(ELECTRONIC SIGNAL PULSATING)
Packer! Packer! Where are you?
Packer! Packer! 你在哪儿？
Vaughn, what have you done to us? What have you done?
Vaughn, 你对我们做了什么？你做了什么？
(HUMMING)
(SCREAMING)
(ELECTRONIC SIGNAL PULSATING)
Vaughn!
Where is the transmitter for the radio beam?
无线电波发射器在哪里？
We can't fight them.
They're too powerful, too many of them.
我们打不过它们的．它们太强大了, 人数太多了
Oh, don't be a fool, man. Where do we turn it off?
噢, 别犯傻了, 伙计．我们在哪里关掉它？
- At the compound, but they'll be there.
- Right. We must stop them.
- 在工业园, 但它们会在那里  - 好, 我们必须阻止它们
Brigadier, Brigadier, this is the Doctor.
准将, 准将, 我是博士
Can you still hear me?
你还能听到我吗？
Yes, Doctor, we heard everything. What do we do?
是的, 博士, 我们都听到了．要我们做什么？
There are only two possibilities.
只有两种可能
We must either cut off the transmitter
of the radio beam at the compound
我们必须要么关掉工业园的无线电波发射器
or destroy the Cyberman spaceship.
要么摧毁赛博人的飞船
How much time do we have?
我们有多少时间？
Oh, I've no idea. It could be minutes or hours.
哦, 我 不知道．有可能是几分钟或者几小时
Depends how long it takes them
to prepare this bomb of theirs.
取决于它们准备那个炸弹要多久
Well, destroying the spaceship
is going to take time.
呃, 摧毁飞船需要不少时间
Then there's only one chance. The radio beam.
那就只有一个机会了, 无线电波
Er, wait. Vaughn.
呃, 等等, Vaughn
Now, Vaughn, will you help us?
现在, Vaughn, 你会帮助我们吗？
We must try to get to the controls
of the radio beam.
我们必须尽力赶到无线电波的控制台
We'll never do it in time unless you help us!
除非有你帮助我们, 否则我们不可能及时赶到！
You still think you have a chance?
你还是觉得你有机会？
- Yes, if you'll help us!  - Help you? Why should I?
- 是的, 只要你肯帮我们！  - 帮你们？我应该吗？
Well, to save us! To save yourself!
对, 救我们！救你自己！
And if I survive, what future have I got?
What will the world do with me?
如果我活下来, 我有什么未来？这个世界会把我怎么样？
Oh, for heaven's sake,
stop thinking about yourself!
噢, 老天啊, 别再只为你自己考虑了！
Think of the millions of people on Earth
who are about to die!
想想地球上亿万的人就要死了！
Appealing to my better nature.
呼唤我人性的一面fixme
No.
不
If I help you, it'll be because I hate them.
如果我帮你, 也只是因为我恨它们
The Cybermen, my ''allies''.
赛博人, 我的同盟
You think I'm mad,
that all I want is power for its own sake.
你觉得我疯了, 我想要的就只是权力本身fixme
No, I have to have power.
不, 我必须得有权力fixme
The world is weak, vulnerable,
a mess of uncoordinated and impossible ideals.
这个世界很虚弱、脆弱, 一团不协调、不现实理念的乱麻fixme
It needs a strong man, a single mind.
它需要一个强人, 一个独立的头脑
- A leader!  - Vaughn, will you listen?
- 一个领袖！  - Vaughn, 你在听吗？
Right.
好
I'll help you to destroy them because I hate them.
我会帮你摧毁它们, 因为我恨它们
They... destroyed my dream.
它们...摧毁了我的梦
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
We must destroy them!
我们必须摧毁它们！
We want to get to
the radio transmitter control room!
我们想要赶到无线电发射器的控制室！
The Cybermen don't know we're here yet.
Let's keep that element of surprise.
赛博人还不知道我们在这里．我们保持这份惊喜吧fixme
Come on, we'll try down here.
快来, 我们试试这下面
(ELECTRONIC SIGNAL PULSATING)
- Now they know we're here.  - Right.
- 现在它们知道我们在这里了  - 对
Up there. We'll go over the roofs.
上那边．我们从屋顶过去
VAUGHN: That's it.
就这样
(PANTING) That's where we've got to get to.
Down there.
那是我们要去的地方, 那下面
Look out!
小心！
(ELECTRONIC SIGNAL PULSATING)
(CLATTERING)
Look out!
小心！
Come on!
快点！
- Is this the only way down?  - Yes.
- 只有这一条路下去吗？  - 是的
Come on, then.
来吧, 那
Cybermen! Take cover!
赛博人！隐蔽！
They've got a main control switch
for the radio beam.
无线电波有一个总开关
There doesn't seem to be
any Cybermen about at all. That's odd.
那周围似乎完全没有赛博人, 这很奇怪
Well, let's not waste time, then.
好, 我们别浪费时间了, 走
Look behind you!
看你后面！
(ELECTRONIC SIGNAL PULSATING)
(SCREAMING)
Whoa!
哇！
(SHOUTING)
Doctor, get down! Right, bazooka!
博士, 下来！好, 火箭炮!
- You all right, Doctor?  - What?
- 你没事吧, 博士？  - 什么？
Yes, yes, it's there, in that building.
是的, 没事, 在那儿, 那栋建筑里
The radio transmitter control,
you've got to destroy it!
无线电发射器, 你得毁掉它！
Leave it to us. Forward!
交给我们吧．前进！
Just a second.
等一下
Oh, but I...
噢, 但是我...
That's it, that's better. Sit still.
就这样, 这样好多了．坐着别东
(GUN FIRING)
(SHOUTING)
BRIGADIER: Grenades!
手雷！
Bazooka!
火箭炮！
That was just a dozen of them.
这才只有十几个
I'd hate to have to meet a hundred.
Forward!
我很讨厌得对付一百个．前进！
前进！
There we are, all done and ready to go.
我们到了．都已经完成, 可以走了
(LAUGHING) Bye-bye.
拜拜
- Bye-bye! - Bye.
- 拜拜！  - 拜
A police box?
一个警亭？
I don't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
(WHOOSHING)
(DOCTOR WHO THEME)